[{"answer": "I was right across by the halls in the library in one of the hallways close to where all the shootings were going on, while the shots were fired.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 9, "question": "Tell me when you were when you realized there was a shooter in the school?", "qSentId": 8}, {"answer": "If -- I believe I knew them both but I'm not going to talk about them right now.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 13, "question": "Did you know either the shooter or the two students who have been injured?", "qSentId": 12}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 16, "question": "We've heard that one of the more seriously wounded students may be a female student, is that the friend that you're talking about?", "qSentId": 15}, {"answer": "No I have not and I'm praying for her and her family that she's going to pull through.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 19, "question": "Have you heard anything?", "qSentId": 18}, {"answer": "I think -- I know were -- I'm personally shocked, I think they are all shocked like you can look around the room that I was in and you could see in every one's eyes that they did not really register what was going on.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 22, "question": "What has been the reaction from your classmates to what has happened today?", "qSentId": 21}, {"answer": "I would like to see some change done.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 31, "question": "It's not just Colorado obviously but with all these shootings, what do you feel should be done to try and combat this?", "qSentId": 30}, {"answer": "My reaction is the American people are much stronger than the voice of the NRA.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 71, "question": "When you're dealing with that kind of mentality and somebody in NRA must have been aware, what is your reaction to that?", "qSentId": 70}, {"answer": "Prayer.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 87, "question": "And also the reason you might be smiling is unlike so many lottery winners you've managed to hang on to you cash, how have you achieved this double miracle?", "qSentId": 86}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 89, "question": "Simple as that, the power of prayer?", "qSentId": 88}, {"answer": "I was having lunch with the kids and I heard kind of second hand through my dad, he had told me that I should probably check it because I didn't even checked the numbers.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 97, "question": "That moment you knew you'd won, where would you and how did you hear?", "qSentId": 96}, {"answer": "I choose to be happy because it's definitely a choice.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 101, "question": "So many lottery winners end up miserable, you seem like one of the happiest people I've ever interviewed?", "qSentId": 100}, {"answer": "I would tell them to live their life, definitely it would put them in a position to be charitable, that is a great thing to do because it also brings that same energy back to you.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 105, "question": "What is the advice you would give for people to win the lottery and stay happy?", "qSentId": 104}, {"answer": "Not yet, not yet, I think I'm going to have one of my kids go buy it for me.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 113, "question": "One last question, have you bought a ticket for tonight?", "qSentId": 112}, {"answer": "No, no, let me start with you Amy, I mean this seemed to me a bafflingly dangerous area for Megyn to go because she's terrific on what she does but not that controversial.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 152, "question": "You met him?", "qSentId": 151}, {"answer": "I have no idea.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "I play though, so is it just a dollar or has it gone up?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well I was, I met Nick on your show which you know and I was just impressed by the way he dealt with things, he already had such a center and I've had this idea for a while that, you know, when this issues happen and unfortunately that keep happening around the country, that it would be great to have a strike force of people that have been through it, who've made it to the other side and a lot of people think your life can never be the same and of course it won't be in one way but it could be in other areas.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 202, "question": "Tell me about the visit and what happened?", "qSentId": 201}, {"answer": "It was a very powerful, powerful event.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 208, "question": "And Nick what was the trip to Newtown like for you and how did you communicate with the people there about what hope they could have going forward?", "qSentId": 207}, {"answer": "Well first of all I've never been about motivation, I know like it's passed around but what I'm really into is uncovering the psychology of what drives somebody and how they can heal.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 213, "question": "Where do you start and how effective do you think you've been in being able to help them with that process?", "qSentId": 212}, {"answer": "It's going great we're meeting with her next week but it's not the money we're contributing, what we really want to do is, he saw this young girl JT, he was hurting, he was still inspired by her that, I mean 12, 13 years old he went out and started to raise money to put her through college because she's supporting an orphan for the orphans.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 229, "question": "ORGAN: And JT actually then, launched a campaign to help people in Rwanda and you contributed I think $10,000 to that Tony, how's that been going, do you know?", "qSentId": 228}, {"answer": "The last time I saw Jesse it was a normal morning like any other, you're getting ready for school and work and Neil was there to pick him up and I walked him out, you know, a little bit late for work and he was a little bit late for work and he was a little bit late for school and turned to talk to Neil about meeting to Gingerbread houses the next day with Jesse and I turned around and I saw that Jesse had written I love you with his fingernail on the frost in my car, a little heart all over the windows and I was just moved and I knew that, that was one of life's moment.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 248, "question": "The buildup to this anniversary for you and all the families must be in many ways excruciating I would imagine but take me back to a year ago, the last time that you saw him and what happened?", "qSentId": 247}, {"answer": "Well that was a long day at the firehouse and I think in some ways that was almost a blessing because we spend all day not really having a lot of information but of course the longer the time went without Jesse, kind of reality was sinking in, so I had a long time to think about it, to think about my life if Jesse wasn't coming back.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "When you heard what had happened and the full scale of the horror hit home, how do you possibly come to terms with it in that moment?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "EWIS: No that was three days after the shooting and we -- all the families met with him at the Newtown High School.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "Because it's obviously it's not something you probably ever imagined you'd be doing with the President of the United States and drawn together in such appalling circumstances?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 276, "question": "And when you heard that about him, that must have been some comfort to you that your boy in that horribly dark moment had shown such extraordinary initiative and bravery?", "qSentId": 275}, {"answer": "So, all of his school work was taken out of his desk in chronological order and put in a box and brought home about a week after he died.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 284, "question": "When you saw that what do you think of it?", "qSentId": 283}, {"answer": "He is incredible.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 316, "question": "You should be very proud of JT for his commitment to this?", "qSentId": 315}, {"answer": "You know, I was -- after the Boston Bombing, I traveled up to the Louis Brown Peace Institute in Dorchester and that is where little Martin's family was from.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 336, "question": "Tell me why he inspired you in particular?", "qSentId": 335}, {"answer": "You know, I truly believe that Jesse's message of nurturing healing love is going to change the world.", "docId": "131213pmt", "aSentId": 348, "question": "How do you find the strength to do what you do, to be out there front and center campaigning in such a positive way?", "qSentId": 347}]